zonpages.com 2019-02-23

# Privacy policy - ZonPages.com

### Effective Date: January 25th, 2017

Disclaimer: ZonPages is in no way affiliated with Amazon or any of it's subsidiaries.

ZonPages considers user privacy paramount, and ZonPages utilizes great care in keeping the information of the customer and/or user (“Customer”) private and secure. To demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy, the following agreement has been created to explain our policies and procedures in relation to all data collected.

#### Types of Data Collected

ZonPages collects data related to our users through the following methods:

  1. Communication protocols and cookies
  2. Online registration and online signup forms
  3. Sales inquiries and transactions
  4. Amazon Seller Information through Amazon MWS
  5. Third party sources of information
  6. Online Customer communications
  7. Offline communications and interactions

#### Internal Use of Information

We accept and gather information in an effort to provide the Service to you. We may also use this information to help us develop and improve our Service, fulfill your requests, send materials to you, inform you about our offers, tailor our Service to meet your interests, and for other purposes permitted by law.

#### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

#### Links

Our Service may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When you leave our Service to visit another website or application, please read the privacy statements of websites that may collect personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Service.

#### Security

We employ procedural and technical safeguards to secure your personal information against loss, theft, alteration, and unauthorized access, use and disclosure. We also employ security procedures to protect your information from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. Regardless of the precautions we take, no transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

#### E-Mail and Electronic Newsletters

We may offer electronic newsletters and e-mails concerning promotions, new products and services, or other marketing materials as a service to our users. You may receive newsletters and e-mails concerning promotions and marketing of ours, after you register through with the Service. If, after you have received a message, you no longer wish to receive such materials, you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each electronic newsletter and e-mail.

#### Access and Control

Some of the information collected about you will be retrievable and changeable through your username login. To do so, follow instructions on the Service.

#### Enforcement

ZonPages has established internal mechanisms to verify its ongoing adherence to its privacy policy. ZonPages also encourages individuals covered by this privacy policy to raise any concerns about our processing of personal information by contacting ZonPages at the address below. ZonPages will seek to resolve any concerns.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Zonpages has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

ZonPages.com  
108 West 13th Street  
Wilmington, DE, USA

Email: support __zonpages.com
